[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
business will be guided and protected
and of course maybe it's obviously
profitable
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
we are not your traditional company
insurance company we are digital
organization or digital company we at
aspire to really serve you know and have
that better service for our customers 24
7.
why FW
right what is so special about us we are
a young company
but we're not small we're already in 10
countries including Philippines in
Philippines but we are celebrating our
eighth year here but already last year
we are already the top five insurers in
Philippines
[Music]
the vision is changing the way people
feel about insurance
we wanted more people to understand how
to make use of their money and the
importance of being financially
protected
we are coming in we're coming in a big
way and we want to serve the top of my
community so on behalf of FWD maraming
maraming salamat thank you again